[
    {
        "Question":"A 22-year-old man has been stabbed In the left fifth intercostal space at the edge of the  sternum. Which structure is most likely to have been penetrated?",
        "Option 1":"Left atrium",
        "Option 2":"Left lobe of the liver",
        "Option 3":"Left ventricle",
        "Option 4":"Right atrium",
        "Option 5":"Right ventricle",
        "Correct Answer":"Right ventricle"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which part of the heart makes the anterior wall of the heart?",
        "Option 1":"Mostly made of right ventricle",
        "Option 2":"Mostly made for left ventricle",
        "Option 3":"Mostly made of right atrium",
        "Option 4":"Mostly made of left atrium",
        "Option 5":"Mostly from left ventricle and left atrium",
        "Correct Answer":"Mostly made of right ventricle"
    },
    {
        "Question":"23 years s brought to ER with perforating anterior chest wound. Which one of the  following about the anterior chest of the heart?",
        "Option 1":"It has its right border formed mainly be left ventricle",
        "Option 2":"It has a coronary sinus passing across it",
        "Option 3":"It is directly related to diaphragm",
        "Option 4":"It mainly formed by left atrium and left ventricle",
        "Option 5":"It mainly formed by right atrium and right ventricle",
        "Correct Answer":"It mainly formed by right atrium and right ventricle"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 25 years old man is stabbed on right side of heart in 4th intercostal space next to  sternum, which structures mostly to be injured?",
        "Option 1":"Left atrium",
        "Option 2":"Left lobe of the liver",
        "Option 3":"Left ventricle",
        "Option 4":"Right atrium",
        "Option 5":"Right ventricle",
        "Correct Answer":"Right atrium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 27 years old man after rood traffic accident has fracture sternum, which structures  mostly to be injured?",
        "Option 1":"Left atrium",
        "Option 2":"Left lobe of the liver",
        "Option 3":"Left ventricle",
        "Option 4":"Right atrium",
        "Option 5":"Right ventricle",
        "Correct Answer":"Right ventricle"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 25 years old man presented after stab knife penetrates the midline of the sternal angle,  which structure is mostly injured?",
        "Option 1":"Trachea",
        "Option 2":"Esophagus",
        "Option 3":"Superior vena cava",
        "Option 4":"Azygous",
        "Option 5":"Vagus",
        "Correct Answer":"Superior vena cava"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 25 years old man presented after stab knife penetrates right to sternal angle and  directed inferior, which structure is mostly injured?",
        "Option 1":"Aorta",
        "Option 2":"IVC",
        "Option 3":"Right atrium",
        "Option 4":"Right brachiocephalic vein",
        "Option 5":"Left brachiocephalic vein",
        "Correct Answer":"Right atrium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 58-year-old man, admitted for inguinal hernia surgery, is found to have an enlarged  heart shadow on his chest radiograph. Which one of the following statements Is true of  the right ventricle?",
        "Option 1":"Has a muscular wall that is normally thicker than that of the Left ventricle",
        "Option 2":"Forms the apex of the heart",
        "Option 3":"Forms the right border of the heart",
        "Option 4":"Is directly related to the diaphragm",
        "Option 5":"Gives rise to the aorta",
        "Correct Answer":"Is directly related to the diaphragm"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 23-year-old man presents to the Emergency Department with non-specific chest pain. A  postero-anterior (PA) chest radiograph is performed and it is normal. Immediately inferior  to the outline of the aortic knuckle was a farther structure with a convex border. What is  this structure?",
        "Option 1":"The left atrium",
        "Option 2":"The pulmonary trunk",
        "Option 3":"The oesophagus",
        "Option 4":"The right atrium",
        "Option 5":"The superior vena cava",
        "Correct Answer":"The pulmonary trunk"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which part of the heart Is related to the dlaphragm?",
        "Option 1":"Right Atrium",
        "Option 2":"Rfight ventricle",
        "Option 3":"Ltatrium",
        "Option 4":"Left ventricle",
        "Option 5":"Left ventricle and right ventricle",
        "Correct Answer":"Left ventricle and right ventricle"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which is correct related to anterior surface of the heart",
        "Option 1":"Left ventricle giving aorta",
        "Option 2":"Pulmonary artery infundibulum from right ventricle",
        "Option 3":"Right coronary artery give inter-ventricular artery",
        "Option 4":"Circumflex anastomosis with right coronary artery",
        "Option 5":"The left atrium form the base of the heart",
        "Correct Answer":"Pulmonary artery infundibulum from right ventricle"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 26 years-old man has stab to right of sternal angle. Which of these structures is least  Injured?",
        "Option 1":"SVC",
        "Option 2":"Arch of aorta",
        "Option 3":"Right atrium",
        "Option 4":"Right brachiocephalic vein",
        "Option 5":"Thoracic duct",
        "Correct Answer":"Thoracic duct"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 20 years old man is stabbed in the left fifth intercostal space. He is tachycardic but with normal blood pressure. His chest X-ray is normal. What is the next step?",
        "Option 1":"Arrange an echocardiogram",
        "Option 2":"Arrange emergency thoracotomy in the operating theatre",
        "Option 3":"Carry out an ECG",
        "Option 4":"Insert a chest drain on the side of the injury",
        "Option 5":"Insert a chest drain on the side of the injury with the addition of high pressure suction",
        "Correct Answer":"Arrange an echocardiogram"
    },
    {
        "Question":"After chest trauma, A 50 years-old man develops signs of cardiac tamponade (low blood pressure, increase jugular venous pressure and muffled heart sound). What is the site for drainage or pericardiocentesis?",
        "Option 1":"Left 5th intercostal midaxillary line",
        "Option 2":"Left 5th intercostal midclavicular line",
        "Option 3":"Left 5th intercostal parasternal line",
        "Option 4":"Left 4th intercostal midclavicular line",
        "Option 5":"Left 4th intercostal parasternal line",
        "Correct Answer":"Left 5th intercostal parasternal line"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 30 years old patient brought to ER with history of RTA his Echo showing  cardiac Tamponade for which pericardiocentesis was done what is the proper site of  Insertion?",
        "Option 1":"Between Xephoid process and left sternocostal margin",
        "Option 2":"Between Xephoid process and right sternocostal margin",
        "Option 3":"Safety triangle in the chest",
        "Option 4":"Right 2nd intercostal space",
        "Option 5":"Right 4th intercostal space",
        "Correct Answer":"Between Xephoid process and left sternocostal margin"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 54 years-old man suffered from chylothorax after thoracotomy for esophagectomy  for removal of esophageal cancer. In which site the Thoracic duct mostly injured?",
        "Option 1":"Before it entered subclavian in neck",
        "Option 2":"At pleural reflection in superior mediastinum",
        "Option 3":"during its course from diaphragm before it reached superior mediastinum",
        "Option 4":"at its crossing in front carotid sheath",
        "Option 5":"none of the above",
        "Correct Answer":"during its course from diaphragm before it reached superior mediastinum"
    },
    {
        "Question":"60 years old develops a chylothorax following esophagectomy. The chest re explored  again for tying of the thoracic duct as it enters the thorax. Where will the ligature be  applied?",
        "Option 1":"At aortic opening",
        "Option 2":"At inferior vena cava hiatus",
        "Option 3":"At site of oesphageal hiatus",
        "Option 4":"Behind the ascending aorta",
        "Option 5":"Lateral to hemiazygos vein",
        "Correct Answer":"At aortic opening"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 75 years old woman have thoracic vertebra collapse secondary to osteoporosis, which of the following structures is in contact with T5 vertebra",
        "Option 1":"Ascending aorta",
        "Option 2":"Azygous vein",
        "Option 3":"Left atrium",
        "Option 4":"Superior vena cava",
        "Option 5":"Tracheal bifurcation",
        "Correct Answer":"Azygous vein"
    },
    {
        "Question":"All of the following are content of the posterior mediastinum except:",
        "Option 1":"Esophagus",
        "Option 2":"Vagus",
        "Option 3":"Thoracic duct",
        "Option 4":"Azygos vein",
        "Option 5":"Vertebral body",
        "Correct Answer":"Vertebral body"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 54 years old man suffered from esophageal cancer. During esophagectomy operation,  the operating surgeon injured thoracic duct. In which part of the thorax chyle will be  collected?",
        "Option 1":"Middle mediastinum",
        "Option 2":"Posterior mediastinum",
        "Option 3":"Pericardium",
        "Option 4":"Visceral pleura",
        "Option 5":"Anterior mediastinum",
        "Correct Answer":"Posterior mediastinum"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which of these structures cannot be seen in axial view on CT of the superior mediastinum?",
        "Option 1":"Left atrium",
        "Option 2":"Esophagus",
        "Option 3":"Trachea",
        "Option 4":"Aortic arch",
        "Option 5":"Superior vena cava",
        "Correct Answer":"Left atrium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 45 years old man with history of mitral valve stenosis, now presented by dysphagia.  Which structure of the following cause dysphagia?",
        "Option 1":"Pulmonary trunk",
        "Option 2":"Left atrium",
        "Option 3":"Right atrium",
        "Option 4":"Aorta",
        "Option 5":"Right ventricle",
        "Correct Answer":"Left atrium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"The phrenic nerve enters the neck from thorax. Which structure is medial to phrenic nerve?",
        "Option 1":"Trachea",
        "Option 2":"SVC",
        "Option 3":"Esophagus",
        "Option 4":"Subclavian artery",
        "Option 5":"Right brachiocephalic vein",
        "Correct Answer":"Right brachiocephalic vein"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which of the following are true about phrenic nerve?",
        "Option 1":"It is only motor nerve",
        "Option 2":"is nerve root is C3, C4 and C5 and mainly from C4",
        "Option 3":"it has sensory supply to lateral part of parietal pleura",
        "Option 4":"right phrenic pass in front of subclavian artery and lateral to aortic arch",
        "Option 5":"It pass behind the hilum of lung",
        "Correct Answer":"is nerve root is C3, C4 and C5 and mainly from C4"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which structure is posterior to the right lung hilum?",
        "Option 1":"Phrenic nerve",
        "Option 2":"Recurrent laryngeal nerve",
        "Option 3":"Glossopharyngeal nerve",
        "Option 4":"Accessory nerve",
        "Option 5":"Esophagus",
        "Correct Answer":"Esophagus"
    },
    {
        "Question":"During esophagectomy operation, there is diaphragm elevation postoperative. Which  nerve is mainly injured?",
        "Option 1":"Vagus nerve",
        "Option 2":"Phrenic nerve",
        "Option 3":"Recurrent laryngeal nerve",
        "Option 4":"Superior laryngeal nerve",
        "Option 5":"Accessory nerve",
        "Correct Answer":"Phrenic nerve"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A surgeon doing operation at posterior triangle of neck. Which structure pass anterior  to scalene muscle in the posterior triangle?",
        "Option 1":"Phrenic nerve",
        "Option 2":"Accessory nerve",
        "Option 3":"Cervical plexus",
        "Option 4":"External jugular vein",
        "Option 5":"Subclavian artery",
        "Correct Answer":"Phrenic nerve"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Heart valve is composed of which of following structure?",
        "Option 1":"Dense fibrous tissue",
        "Option 2":"Hyaline cartilage",
        "Option 3":"Smooth muscle",
        "Option 4":"Fibrocartilage",
        "Option 5":"Skeletal muscle",
        "Correct Answer":"Dense fibrous tissue"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Mechanical prosthesis is seen in right 3rd intercostal space. Which valve may be this prosthesis?",
        "Option 1":"Aortic valve",
        "Option 2":"Mitral valve",
        "Option 3":"Tricuspid valve",
        "Option 4":"Pulmonary valve",
        "Option 5":"Patent ductus arteriosus",
        "Correct Answer":"Aortic valve"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A young girl presented with murmur at left 2nd intercostal space, which valve of these  valves is mostly affected?",
        "Option 1":"Aortic",
        "Option 2":"Pulmonary",
        "Option 3":"Mitral",
        "Option 4":"ASD",
        "Option 5":"Tricuspid",
        "Correct Answer":"Pulmonary"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the site of the pulmonary valve auscultated?",
        "Option 1":"Right 2nd intercostal space",
        "Option 2":"Left 2nd intercostal space",
        "Option 3":"Left 5th intercostal space",
        "Option 4":"Right 5th intercostal space",
        "Option 5":"Xiphisterna",
        "Correct Answer":"Left 2nd intercostal space"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 50 years old man has myocardial infarction and we found that he has right coronary  thrombosis. Right coronary artery is a branch from which vessel?",
        "Option 1":"Ascending aorta",
        "Option 2":"Arch of aorta",
        "Option 3":"Descending aorta",
        "Option 4":"Coronary sinus",
        "Option 5":"Left coronary artery",
        "Correct Answer":"Ascending aorta"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 52 years old man has myocardial Infarction and we found that he has left coronary thrombosis. Which is true regarding left coronary artery?",
        "Option 1":"It runs behind pulmonary trunk",
        "Option 2":"It runs in anterior interventricular groove",
        "Option 3":"It comes out of aorta just below the valves",
        "Option 4":"It is branch of aortic arch",
        "Option 5":"It has posterior inter-ventricular and marginal branches",
        "Correct Answer":"It runs behind pulmonary trunk"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Regarding venous drainage of the heart. Location of middle cardiac vein in which groove?",
        "Option 1":"Anterior inter-ventricular groove",
        "Option 2":"Posterior inter-ventricular groove",
        "Option 3":"Right atrio-ventricular groove",
        "Option 4":"Left atrio-ventricular groove",
        "Option 5":"At margin of right ventricle",
        "Correct Answer":"Posterior inter-ventricular groove"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A determinant of right coronary or left coronary dominant of the heart is mainly depends  on which structure or branch supply?",
        "Option 1":"AV node supply",
        "Option 2":"SA node supply",
        "Option 3":"Circumflex artery",
        "Option 4":"Right coronary artery",
        "Option 5":"Posterior descending artery",
        "Correct Answer":"Posterior descending artery"
    },
    {
        "Question":"An infant was found having left SVC anomaly, in which vein it will drain its blood?",
        "Option 1":"Oblique sinus",
        "Option 2":"Coronary sinus",
        "Option 3":"Azygos vein",
        "Option 4":"Internal thoracic vein",
        "Option 5":"Right atrium directly",
        "Correct Answer":"Coronary sinus"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 12-year-old child was admitted to the Emergency Department having inhaled a peanut. Where will the peanut most likely to have lodged?",
        "Option 1":"Left lower lobe bronchus",
        "Option 2":"left upper lobe bronchus",
        "Option 3":"Right lower lobe bronchus",
        "Option 4":"Right middle lobe bronchus",
        "Option 5":"Right upper lobe bronchus",
        "Correct Answer":"Right lower lobe bronchus"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 2-vear-old child was admitted to the Emergency Department having Coin ingested and  seen on x-ray somewhere, where will you find it Lodged?",
        "Option 1":"At thyroid level",
        "Option 2":"At hyoid level",
        "Option 3":"At cricopharyngeal level",
        "Option 4":"At heart level",
        "Option 5":"At the carina",
        "Correct Answer":"At cricopharyngeal level"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Child swallows a coin come with difficulty breathing and X-ray show coln at the gastro- osepgheal junction. How far is this from the incisors?",
        "Option 1":"22cm",
        "Option 2":"25 cm",
        "Option 3":"27cm",
        "Option 4":"30cm",
        "Option 5":"40 cm",
        "Correct Answer":"40 cm"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 22-year-old man arrives to the Emergency Department with sudden breathlessness  due to a large pneumothorax. A chest drain is inserted into the fifth left intercostal space  in 5th mid-axillary line. There is blood into the drainage bottle. Which of the following  structures is the most likely cause of this acute hemorrhage?",
        "Option 1":"Intercostal artery",
        "Option 2":"Left pericardiophrenic artery",
        "Option 3":"Lingula of the lung",
        "Option 4":"Right ventricle of the heart",
        "Option 5":"Spleen",
        "Correct Answer":"Intercostal artery"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 22-year-old man arrives to the Emergency Department with sudden breathlessness due  to a large pneumothorax. A chest drain is inserted into the fifth left intercostal space in 5th  mid-axillary line, Innervation of the costal part of the parietal pleura when you put in a  chest tube by which nerve?",
        "Option 1":"Superior laryngeal nerve",
        "Option 2":"Recurrent laryngeal nerve",
        "Option 3":"Intercostal nerves",
        "Option 4":"Phrenic nerve",
        "Option 5":"Vagus nerve",
        "Correct Answer":"Intercostal nerves"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 30 years old man has pneumothorax after RTA. In which space is the site of insertion of  chest tube?",
        "Option 1":"4th intercostal midaxillary line",
        "Option 2":"4th intercostal midclavicular line",
        "Option 3":"5th intercostal midaxillary line",
        "Option 4":"5th intercostal midclavicular line",
        "Option 5":"6th intercostal midclavicular line",
        "Correct Answer":"5th intercostal midaxillary line"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What are the boundaries of the correct site for intercostal chest drain insertion?",
        "Option 1":"Pectoralis major, serratus and line through the nipple",
        "Option 2":"Pectoralis minor, serratus and line through nipple",
        "Option 3":"Pectoralis major, latissimus dorsi and line through the nipple",
        "Option 4":"Pectoralis minor, latissimus dorsi and line through nipple",
        "Option 5":"None of the above",
        "Correct Answer":"Pectoralis major, latissimus dorsi and line through the nipple"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A young girl presented with hyperhidrosis. Thoracoscoplc surgery Is done for treatment of  hyperhidrosis, what is the most common complication?",
        "Option 1":"Phrenic nerve injury",
        "Option 2":"Horner syndrome",
        "Option 3":"Vagus nerve injury",
        "Option 4":"Oculomotor nerve injury",
        "Option 5":"Accessory nerve injury",
        "Correct Answer":"Horner syndrome"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the main muscle working in quiet inspiration?",
        "Option 1":"Diaphragm",
        "Option 2":"Internal intercostal",
        "Option 3":"External intercostal",
        "Option 4":"Serratus anterior",
        "Option 5":"Sternomastoid muscle",
        "Correct Answer":"Diaphragm"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is true about Left internal thoracic artery?",
        "Option 1":"Immediate branch at origin of subclavian artery",
        "Option 2":"Second branch after vertebral artery",
        "Option 3":"Third branch of subclavian artery",
        "Option 4":"Not branch from subclavian artery",
        "Option 5":"Branch from ascending aorta",
        "Correct Answer":"Second branch after vertebral artery"
    },
    {
        "Question":"29 year old man has posterior right 8th rib fracture inward cause injury of which structure?",
        "Option 1":"Liver",
        "Option 2":"Right lower lung",
        "Option 3":"IVC",
        "Option 4":"Pulmonary",
        "Option 5":"Hemiazygos",
        "Correct Answer":"Right lower lung"
    },
    {
        "Question":"50 year old man presented by middle lobe lung mass and needed to take biopsy for diagnosis of that mass. From which space we can take biopsy by needle?",
        "Option 1":"4th intercostal space midaxillary line",
        "Option 2":"6th intercostal space midaxillary line",
        "Option 3":"7th intercostal space mid clavicular line",
        "Option 4":"5th intercostal space mid clavicular line",
        "Option 5":"4th space parasternal line",
        "Correct Answer":"5th intercostal space mid clavicular line"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 22-year-old man has been stabbed in the left fifth intercostal space at the edge of the  sternum. Which structure is most likely to have been penetrated?",
        "Option 1":"Esophagus",
        "Option 2":"Pericardium",
        "Option 3":"Aorta",
        "Option 4":"Pleura",
        "Option 5":"Pulmonary trunk",
        "Correct Answer":"Pericardium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"45 years old patient has chest lesion and require needle aspiration. While doing needle  aspiration in second Intercostal space midclavicular line, what is the structure damaged?",
        "Option 1":"2nd  intercostal nerve",
        "Option 2":"3rd  intercostal nerve",
        "Option 3":"Internal thoracic artery",
        "Option 4":"thoracoacromial artery",
        "Option 5":"Epigastric artery",
        "Correct Answer":"2nd  intercostal nerve"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A young girl presented with hyperhidrosis. Thoracoscopic surgery is done for treatment of  hyperhidrosis; stellate ganglion is injured causing Horner syndrome. What are level of  Ganglion forms stellate?",
        "Option 1":"C6-C7",
        "Option 2":"C7-T1",
        "Option 3":"T1-T2",
        "Option 4":"T2-T3",
        "Option 5":"T3-T4",
        "Correct Answer":"C7-T1"
    },
    {
        "Question":"60 years old patient has sternal dehiscence after CABG is performed. There was wound on sternum and prepared for muscle flap. Now sternum blood supply depends on which vessel?",
        "Option 1":"Thoracoacromial artery",
        "Option 2":"Internal thoracic artery",
        "Option 3":"Intercostal arteries",
        "Option 4":"Axillary artery",
        "Option 5":"Abdominal aorta",
        "Correct Answer":"Intercostal arteries"
    },
    {
        "Question":"35 years old man with rheumatic mitral stenosis developed mitral valve regurge after failed balloon valvuloplasty to the mitral valve, now will be undergoing surgical repair for mitral regurge, what can be a complication?",
        "Option 1":"Left Circumflex artery injury",
        "Option 2":"Bundle branch block",
        "Option 3":"Posterior descending artery injury",
        "Option 4":"Right coronary artery injury",
        "Option 5":"None of the above",
        "Correct Answer":"Left Circumflex artery injury"
    },
    {
        "Question":"40 years old patient developed hemothorax or pleural effusion after RTA and he has chest pain radiation to abdomen, which nerve is affected mainly?",
        "Option 1":"Intercostal nerve",
        "Option 2":"Phrenic nerve",
        "Option 3":"Vagus nerve",
        "Option 4":"Splanchnic nerve",
        "Option 5":"Pelvic nerve",
        "Correct Answer":"Intercostal nerve"
    },
    {
        "Question":"50 years old man has advanced esophageal cancer an in follow up, there is  compression anterior to structure at level of T3. what is the structure may be compressed?",
        "Option 1":"Left atrium",
        "Option 2":"Right ventricle",
        "Option 3":"Trachea",
        "Option 4":"Thoracic duct",
        "Option 5":"Left bronchus",
        "Correct Answer":"Trachea"
    },
    {
        "Question":"A 3 years old child was admitted to the Emergency Department having inhaled a  foreign body. Where will the foreign body most likely to have lodged?",
        "Option 1":"Left upper lobe bronchus",
        "Option 2":"Middle lobe bronchus",
        "Option 3":"Right lower lobe bronchus",
        "Option 4":"Right upper lobe bronchus",
        "Option 5":"Right main bronchus",
        "Correct Answer":"Right main bronchus"
    },
    {
        "Question":"5 years old female with history of left renal mass about 10 cm then presented with  dullness of percussion on the left side and her chest X-ray is attached. What is your  management?",
        "Option 1":"Chest tube insertion",
        "Option 2":"2nd  intercostal midclavicular needle insertion",
        "Option 3":"Pleural aspiration",
        "Option 4":"2nd  intercostal midaxillary tube insertion",
        "Option 5":"5th  intercostal midaxillary tube insertion",
        "Correct Answer":"Pleural aspiration"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which structure passed with esophagus through dlaphragm?",
        "Option 1":"Phrenic nerve",
        "Option 2":"Left vagus nerve",
        "Option 3":"Intercostal nerve",
        "Option 4":"Thoracic duct",
        "Option 5":"Azygos nerve",
        "Correct Answer":"Left vagus nerve"
    },
    {
        "Question":"59.A 27 years old man alleged blunt trauma to midline sub xiphold which structures mostly to be injured?",
        "Option 1":"Left atrium",
        "Option 2":"Left lobe of the liver",
        "Option 3":"Left ventricle",
        "Option 4":"Right atrium",
        "Option 5":"Right ventricle",
        "Correct Answer":"Left lobe of the liver"
    },
    {
        "Question":"60 years old man has esophageal mass detected by upper endoscopy about 24 cm from incisor. To which lymph node this mass drain?",
        "Option 1":"Trachea-esophageal",
        "Option 2":"Celiac",
        "Option 3":"Parasternal",
        "Option 4":"Deep cervical",
        "Option 5":"Supraclavicular",
        "Correct Answer":"Trachea-esophageal"
    },
    {
        "Question":"35 years old patient suffered from dyspnea and palpitation. On examination, there ls holosystolic murmur propagate to axilla. What is the expected chamber enlargement in transesophageal echo?",
        "Option 1":"Left atrium",
        "Option 2":"Left ventricle",
        "Option 3":"Right ventricle",
        "Option 4":"Right atrium",
        "Option 5":"Ventricle apex",
        "Correct Answer":"Left atrium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"50 years old patient with chest pain and ECG show inversion of T wave in V4 and diagnosed as anterior lateral Non-STEMI and now heart rate becomes 40. What is the affected part cause bradycardia?",
        "Option 1":"Bundle of Hiss",
        "Option 2":"SA node",
        "Option 3":"Cardiac plexus",
        "Option 4":"Great cardiac vein",
        "Option 5":"Middle cardiac vein",
        "Correct Answer":"Bundle of Hiss"
    }
]